# **Denis Tovstokhatko**

# **Frontend Developer**

## **Personal summary**

Hey! I'm Denis - a self-educated and enthusiastic front-end developer from Kyiv.

I consider myself as a person who always moves forward to new opportunities, knowledge and experiences that is why I am extremely interested in web development, which has already equipped me with skills and attitudes required for a successful professional career.

Believe in producing high-quality work, that fuels the engagement between WEB and his audience. Passions - music, sport and technology.

Works: dentov13.github.io

# **Career History**

January 2017 - September 2017 (9 month)

**HTML Coder / Frontend Developer** 

Skywell LLC - skywell.com.ua

February 2016 - December 2016 (11 month)

Web-developer

Audit firm "Alliance" - alliance.co.ua

October 2015 - December 2015 (3 month)

**Trainee / Junior Frontend Developer** 

IT-Mentor — pet-project from community of dou.ua

## **Education**

November 2016 - January 2017

JavaScript Advanced course (Certificate), CBS

<u>August 2016 - Winter 2017-2018 (in progress)</u>

Master in Computer Science, KNUTE

September 2012 - June 2016

**Bachelor** in **Economic Cybernetics**, KNUTE

## **Skills**

- HTML 5, CSS 3
- SASS / SCSS, LESS
- PostCSS
- BEM methodology
- Bootstrap
- Git
- jQuery
- JavaScript (ES5 / ES6 / ES7)
- REST API
- HTTP Requests
- AJAX
- Babel
- React.js
- Redux
- React Router
- Ramda
- Gulp, Webpack
- Bower
- Node.js / Express
- npm / yarn
- WordPress (inc. backend)
- PHP

## Other Skills

- Software Design Patterns
- Adobe Photoshop / Sketch
- Avocode / Zeplin
- Github / Bitbucket
- Terminal
- Cross-browser development
- Technical curiosity
- Affinity for detail
- Intermediate English

#### **Contacts**

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine
Birthday: 13 October 1995
Mobile: +380(93) 019 05 40
Portfolio: dentov13.github.io
Mail: tovstokhatko.denis@gmail.com







